foreign
but the essence of this entire
initiative was acceptance of our
differences the four main topics what we
have chosen it had a very big background
behind it the feedback and the kind of
reaction that we were getting from the
employees is pretty heartwarming we got
this opportunity to take a part in this
program and gave me a chance to actually
engage with the different people
different verticals I just want to thank
the team I got a chance to engage with
everyone The Artsy team we are very
thankful for them they refined us with
thought like okay
how the voice modulation has to be done
how the facial expressions and how you
have to engage the audience also if the
employees are happy the productivity is
better it's a National Organization you
know from Jammu and Kashmir to
kanyakumari people working from Kerala
uh from North India people working from
Delhi they are working in Kerala
diversity we are living in it